<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://localhost:4000/rccpii-2018/assets/xslt/rss.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://localhost:4000/rccpii-2018/assets/css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>The Rural Campus Connectivity Project 2018</title>
		<description>The Rural Campus Connectivity Project (RCCP II) is funded by the DHET, managed by Universities South Africa (USAF) and implemented by the Tertiary Research and Education Network (TENET) of SA. The capacity development initiatives are managed by Talarify. We aim to bring connectivity to tertiary education and research institutions and help them foster a culture of collaborative connectedness.</description>
		<link>http://localhost:4000/rccpii-2018/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/rccpii-2018/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>First Carpentry Instructor Training for 2018</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/rccpii-2018/carpentries/instructor/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;In 2016 and 2017 three Software, Data, and Library Carpentry instructor training events 
were run in South Africa. These train-the-trainers events were well-attended by researchers, 
IT staff as well as librarians. Participants came from a wide range of universities and companies from all over the country and even from other African countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://carpentries.github.io/instructor-training/&quot;&gt;Carpentry instructor training&lt;/a&gt; aims to teach those who can already use tools such as R, Python, Shell, Git, Matlab, and 
OpenRefine, to become better teachers of these tools. The Carpentries’ lessons are specifically aimed
at people who work in research settings. The training includes topics such as assessment, how learning works, how to organise and run a Carpentry workshop, and more. It does not teach the tools itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about Software, Data, and Library Carpentry, please see:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://software-carpentry.org/&quot;&gt;Software Carpentry&lt;/a&gt; (typically for people who develop research software as part of their research/work/studies)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.datacarpentry.org/&quot;&gt;Data Carpentry&lt;/a&gt; (typically for people who analyse data as part of their research/work/studies)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://librarycarpentry.github.io/&quot;&gt;Library Carpentry&lt;/a&gt; (typically for librarians who want to learn new ways of supporting researchers and being more productive in their work)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More information and the application form link is available on &lt;a href=&quot;https://tenet-rccpii.github.io/2018-02-21-South-Africa-ttt/&quot;&gt;the course website&lt;/a&gt;. Please add as much information to the application form to help us 
understand why you would be a good candidate for the training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The workshop is funded by the DHET through RCCP II.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Application deadline&lt;/em&gt;: 17:00 SAST 31 January 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;t60&quot; id=&quot;other-post-formats&quot;&gt;Other Post Formats&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    

  
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/rccpii-2018/carpentries/instructor/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
